<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Tensorlet</title>
  
  <subtitle>Tensor Theory and Deep Learning Technology</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://summerhh1031.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2018-07-15T14:18:19.487Z</updated>
  <id>https://summerhh1031.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Tensorlet</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Selected Publications</title>
    <link href="https://summerhh1031.github.io/Selected-Publications/"/>
    <id>https://summerhh1031.github.io/Selected-Publications/</id>
    <published>2018-01-29T15:55:01.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-07-15T14:18:19.487Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul><li>Haotian Zhou, Xiao-Yang Liu, Cai Fu, Chen Shang, and Xinyi Chang. Differentially Private Matrix Completion via Distributed Matrix Factorization. IEEE TrustCom 2018.</li><li>Hongyang Yang, Xiao-Yang Liu, Qingwei Wu. A Practical Machine Learning Approach for Dynamic Stock Recommendation. IEEE TrustCom 2018.</li><li>Tao Deng, Feng Qian,  Xiao-Yang Liu, Manyuan Zhang, Anwar Walid. Tensor Sensing for RF Tomographic Imaging. ICME 2018. [ <a href="../../download/Dengtao_ICME_Tensor_Sensing.zip" download="Dengtao_ICME_Tensor_Sensing.zip">Code</a> ] and [ <a href="../../download/Dengtao_ICME_Tensor_Sensing.pdf" download="Dengtao_ICME_Tensor_Sensing.pdf">Slides</a> ]</li><li>Tao Zhang, Da Xu and Xiao-Yang Liu. cuTensor: Efficient Low-tubal-rank Tensor Completion on GPUs. (CUDA Implementaion)  [ <a href="../../download/Zhangtao_cuTensorLib_2018.zip" download="Zhangtao_cuTensorLib_2018.zip">Library Codes</a> ].</li><li>Chenxiao Zhu, Lingqing Xu, Xiao-Yang Liu, Feng Qian. Tensor-Generative Adversarial Network with Two-dimensional Sparse Coding: Application to Real-time Indoor Localization. IEEE International Conference on Communications (ICC) 2018. [ <a href="../../download/ZhuChenxiao_ICC_2017_data.zip" download="ZhuChenxiao_ICC_2017_data.zip">Data</a> ] and [ <a href="../../download/ZhuChenxiao_ICC_2017_slides.zip" download="ZhuChenxiao_ICC_2017_slides.zip">Slides</a> ]</li><li>Fei Jiang, Xiao-Yang Liu, Hongtao Lu, Ruimin Shen. Efficient Multi-dimensional Tensor Sparse Coding Using t-linear Combinations. AAAI 2018. [ <a href="../../download/Jiangfei_AAAI_2018_Poster.pdf" download="Jiangfei_AAAI_2018_Poster.pdf">Poster</a> ] and [<a href="../../download/Jiangfei_AAAI_2018_PPT.pdf" download="Jiangfei_AAAI_2018_PPT.pdf">Slides</a>]</li><li>Feng Qian, Miao Yin, Xiao-Yang Liu, Yao-Jun Wang, Cai Lu, and Guang-Min Hu. Unsupervised Seismic Facies Analysis via Deep Convolutional Autoencoders. Geophysics, 2018.</li><li>Cuiping Li, Yue Sun, Xiao-Yang Liu, Ying Li. Tensor Subspace Detection with Tubal-sampling and Elementwise-sampling. IEEE ICASSP 2018. [ <a href="../../download/Licuiping_ICASSP_2018_code.rar" download="Licuiping_ICASSP_2018_code.rar">Code</a> ]</li></ul><ul><li><p>Fei Jiang, Xiao-Yang Liu, Hongtao Lu, Ruimin Shen. Anisotropic Total Variation Regularized Low-rank Tensor Completion based on Tensor Nuclear Norm for Color Image Inpainting. IEEE ICASSP 2018.</p></li><li><p>Fei Jiang, Huating Li, Xuhong Hou, Bin Sheng, Ruimin Shen, Xiao-Yang Liu, Weiping Jia, Ping Li, Ruogu Fang: Abdominal Adipose Tissues Extraction Using Multi-scale Deep Neural Network. Neurocomputing 229: 23-33, 2017.</p></li><li><p>Fei Jiang, Xiao-Yang Liu, Hongtao Lu, Ruimin Shen. Graph Regularized Tensor Sparse Coding for Image Representation. IEEE ICME 2017.</p></li><li><p>Xiao-Yang Liu, Xiaodong Wang. LS-Decomposition for Robust Recovery of Sensory Big Data. IEEE Transactions on Big Data, 2017.</p></li><li><p>Xiao-Yang Liu and Xiaodong Wang. Fourth-order tensor space with two-dimensional discrete transforms. arXiv 2017 <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1705.01576" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://arxiv.org/abs/1705.01576</a></p></li><li><p>Xiao-Yang Liu, Shuchin Aeron, Vaneet Aggarwal, Xiaodong Wang. Low-tubal-rank Tensor Completion using Alternating Minimization. (Submitted to) IEEE Transactions on Information Theory. arXiv 2016: <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1610.01690" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://arxiv.org/abs/1610.01690</a> [ <a href="../../download/LiuXiaoyang_TIT_2016_code.rar" download="LiuXiaoyang_TIT_2016_code.rar">both MATLAB codes and CUDA codes</a> ].</p></li><li><p>Yao Xie, Xiao-Yang Liu, Linghe Kong, Fan Wu, Guihai Chen, Athanasios V Vasilakos. Drone-Based Wireless Relay Using Online Tensor Update. IEEE 22nd International Conference on Parallel and Distributed Systems (ICPADS), 2016.</p></li><li><p>Xiao-Yang Liu, Shuchin Aeron, Vaneet Aggarwal, Xiaodong Wang, Min-You Wu. Tensor Completion Via Adaptive Sampling of Tensor Fibers: Application to Efficient Indoor RF Fingerprinting. IEEE ICASSP, 2016.</p></li><li><p>Xiao-Yang Liu, Shuchin Aeron, Vaneet Aggarwal, Xiaodong Wang, Min-You Wu. Adaptive Sampling of RF Fingerprints for Fine-grained Indoor Localization. IEEE Transactions on Mobile Computing, 2016. </p></li><li><p>Linghe Kong, Liang He, Xiao-Yang Liu, Yu Gu, Min-You Wu, Xue Liu. Privacy-Preserving Compressive Sensing for Crowdsensing based Trajectory Recovery. IEEE ICDCS, Columbus, Ohio, USA, 2015.</p></li><li><p>Xiao-Yang Liu, Yanmin Zhu, Linghe Kong, Cong Liu, Yu Gu, Athanasios V. Vasilakos, Min-You Wu. CDC: Compressive Data Collection for Wireless Sensor Networks. IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems, Vol.26, No.8, pp. 2188-2197, 2015.</p></li><li><p>Linghe Kong, Xiao-Yang Liu, Meixia Tao, Min-You Wu, Yu Gu, Long Cheng, Jianwei Niu. Resource-Efficient Data Gathering in Sensor Networks for Environment Reconstruction. The Computer Journal (COMJ), Vol. 58, No. 6, pp. 1330-1343, 2015.</p></li><li><p>Linghe Kong, Mingyuan Xia, Xiao-Yang Liu, Guangshuo Chen, Yu Gu, Min-You Wu, Xue Liu. Data Loss and Reconstruction in Wireless Sensor Networks. IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems, Vol. 25, No. 11, pp. 2818-2828, 2014.</p></li><li><p>Guangshuo Chen, Xiao-Yang Liu, Linghe Kong, Jia-Liang Lu, Min-You Wu. Multi-Attribute Compressive Data Gathering. IEEE WCNC, Istanbul, Turkey, 2014.</p></li><li><p>Linghe Kong, Mingyuan Xia, Xiao-Yang Liu, Guangshuo Chen, Yu Gu, Min-You Wu, Xue Liu. Data Loss and Reconstruction in Wireless Sensor Networks. IEEE Transactions on Parallel and Distributed Systems, Vol. 25, No. 11, pp. 2818-2828, 2014.</p></li><li><p>Guangshuo Chen, Xiao-Yang Liu, Linghe Kong, Jia-Liang Lu, Yu Gu, Wei Shu, Min-You Wu. Multiple Attributes-based Data Recovery in Wireless Sensor Networks. IEEE GlobeCom, Atlanda, GA, USA, 2013.</p></li><li><p>Guangshuo Chen, Xiao-Yang Liu, Linghe Kong, Jia-Liang Lu, Wei Shu, Min-You Wu. JSSDR: Joint-Sparse Sensory Data Recovery in Wireless Sensor Networks. IEEE WiMob, Lyon, France, 2013.</p></li><li><p>Linghe Kong, Mingyuan Xia, Xiao-Yang Liu, Min-You Wu, Xue Liu. Data Loss and Reconstruction in Sensor Networks. IEEE INFOCOM, Turin, Italy, 2013.</p></li></ul>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Haotian Zhou, Xiao-Yang Liu, Cai Fu, Chen Shang, and Xinyi Chang. Differentially Private Matrix Completion via Distributed Matrix F
      
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Publiction" scheme="https://summerhh1031.github.io/categories/Publiction/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
